Hello, everyone. I'm Li Xiaoyu, an intern. I've been an intern for two months. Do you want to know about our internship life?
Hi, my name is Li Xiaoyu. I'm from Shanghai Engineering University.
I majored in Fashion and Art Design. I'm currently studying at Yan San University.
I will graduate in June, 2025.
Before I came here, I had been studying at Close 3D for nearly three years.
And I also took an advanced certificate from Close 3D.
Hello, everyone. I'm Chen Luming.
I'm from Donghua University's Fashion and Art Design School.
I'm a student in the Chinese-Japanese cooperation major.
I took an entrance exam in July this year and came to the Close company for an internship.
My main job is to measure and measure food.
What kind of life does it take to be an intern at Close 3D?
I started my internship with training.
Here I have been dealing with fabric digitization.
The accuracy of fabric digitization is also very important for the restoration of virtual clothing.
In addition, for those who plan to come to Close 3D for an internship,
my suggestion is to have a certain initial ability.
Because Close 3D will have initial ability assessment before the internship.
Everyone can learn related videos on Close 3D's Bilibili and public account.
You can record your own problems.
If you have the opportunity to come to an internship,
you can solve your own problems very accurately and quickly.
You can improve your skills.
Before coming to Close 3D, I did not practice the processing of fabric, physics, and textiles.
I just listened to how to operate in the class.
After coming to Close 3D, I had the guidance and training of all the teachers.
Then I can practice better.
In terms of fabric, it is divided into physics and textiles.
Physical processing is mainly for some of its stretch and curve.
Thickness of the fabric can be measured, and others such as weight and thickness are used for making theapproving.
For particle processing, it is mainly used to make precision scanning,
then this can be applied to all forms of software,
in order to have the more realistic real-time images.
A lot of different types of fabric can be executed in Close 3D time,
so tunneling of the product is truly interesting.
In this process,
I want to make some materials that may not exist in the real world
It can add a lot of design fun
And some possibilities of creation
I hope in the future
I can improve my level of virtual fashion production
And then I hope I can put some of the other software
Some of the 3D scenes are added to the cloud
And then I'm going to do a walkthrough in the cloud
Make the clothes move
What do you think of the future development of the clothing industry
I think in terms of clothing
As a more traditional industry
It needs digital intervention in all aspects
To achieve its efficiency and cost double harvest
The clothing industry
I think it is now in a direction of virtualization
And then like us
That's what we're doing
And then he has a lot of advantages
There are two of them
That is, there is no physical and there is no physical
No physical means that he can
No need
That one
To make a real physical fabric
And it's very convenient and efficient
You don't have to do what we used to do
Factory processing
There's a lot of time and a long cycle to do
We can do our design very quickly
And then you can achieve
Very bold and innovative
Some of the effects of our design
And then it's sustainable
Since he doesn't need real fabric
Then he doesn't have to think about the waste of materials
There are some environmental issues
It's a virtual one
I think this direction is very good
That's a trend in the clothing industry right now
Your future for yourself
What plans do you have
My first major is not to choose clothing
But I found that it has something to do with our lives
So I got interested in it
I will also improve myself through the competition
In September this year
The digital show in Beijing Fashion Week will also have my work
My future plans
It must still be in the clothing industry
But in the clothing industry
I prefer the digitalization of clothing
So I think I will be in the future
I will go further and further in the digitalization of clothing
Hello everyone
I am Andy, a technical expert of Colossandy
As one of the managers of this intern training
I saw their pursuit and love for new technology and new things
Now they can already have quality and efficiency
Complete daily internship tasks
I believe they have a deeper understanding of the new technology and digitalization of the clothing industry
After graduation in the future
Enter the industry
Can also carry out deep applications
Promote the positive development of the industry